Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School [yearbook], 1977; UP150.001.036.00001 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 2, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00005 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 3, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00006 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 4, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00007 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 5, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00008 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 6, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00009 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 7, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00010 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 8, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00011 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 9, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00012 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 10, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00013 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 11, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00014 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 12, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00015 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 13, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00016 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 14, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00017 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 15, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00018 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 16, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00019 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 17, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00020 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 18, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00021 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 19, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00022 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 20, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00023 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 21, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00024 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 22, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00025 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 23, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00026 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 24, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00027 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 25, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00028 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 26, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00029 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 27, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00030 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 28, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00031 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 29, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00032 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 30, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00033 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 31, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00034 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 32, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00035 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 33, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00036 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 34, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00037 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 35, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00038 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 36, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00039 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 37, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00040 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 38, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00041 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 39, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00042 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 40, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00043 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 41, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00044 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 42, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00045 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 43, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00046 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 44, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00047 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 45, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00048 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 46, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00049 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 47, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00050 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 48, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00051 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 49, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00052 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 50, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00053 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 51, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00054 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 52, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00055 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 53, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00056 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 54, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00057 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 55, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00058 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 56, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00059 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 57, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00060 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 58, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00061 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 59, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00062 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 60, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00063 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 61, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00064 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 62, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00065 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 63, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00066 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 64, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00067 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 65, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00068 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 66, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00069 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 67, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00070 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 68, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00071 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 69, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00072 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 70, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00073 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 71, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00074 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 72, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00075 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 73, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00076 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 74, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00077 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 75, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00078 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 76, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00079 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 77, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00080 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 78, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00081 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 79, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00082 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 80, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00083 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 81, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00084 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 82, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00085 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 83, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00086 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 84, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00087 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 85, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00088 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 86, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00089 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 87, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00090 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 88, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00091 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 89, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00092 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 90, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00093 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 91, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00094 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 92, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00095 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 93, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00096 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 94, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00097 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 95, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00098 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 96, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00099 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 97, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00100 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 98, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00101 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 99, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00102 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 100, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00103 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 101, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00104 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 102, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00105 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 103, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00106 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 104, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00107 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 105, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00108 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 106, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00109 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 107, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00110 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 108, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00111 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 109, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00112 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 110, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00113 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 111, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00114 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 112, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00115 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 113, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00116 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 114, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00117 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 115, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00118 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 116, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00119 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 117, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00120 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 118, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00121 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 119, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00122 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, page 120, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00123 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, inside back cover (1), 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00124 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, inside back cover (2), 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00125 (Volume 36)
    - Seventy-seven, Tufts Medical School, back cover, 1977; UP150.001.036.00001.00126 (Volume 36)
  - Tufts Medical 1978 [yearbook], UP150.001.037.00001 (Volume 37)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1978.
    - Tufts Medical 1978, front cover, UP150.001.037.00001.00001 (Volume 37)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1978
    - Tufts Medical 1978, inside front cover (1), UP150.001.037.00001.00002 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, inside front cover (2), UP150.001.037.00001.00003 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 1, UP150.001.037.00001.00004 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 2, UP150.001.037.00001.00005 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 3, UP150.001.037.00001.00006 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 4, UP150.001.037.00001.00007 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 5, UP150.001.037.00001.00008 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 6, UP150.001.037.00001.00009 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 7, UP150.001.037.00001.00010 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 8, UP150.001.037.00001.00011 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 9, UP150.001.037.00001.00012 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 10, UP150.001.037.00001.00013 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 11, UP150.001.037.00001.00014 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 12, UP150.001.037.00001.00015 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 13, UP150.001.037.00001.00016 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 14, UP150.001.037.00001.00017 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 15, UP150.001.037.00001.00018 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 16, UP150.001.037.00001.00019 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 17, UP150.001.037.00001.00020 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 18, UP150.001.037.00001.00021 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 19, UP150.001.037.00001.00022 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 20, UP150.001.037.00001.00023 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 21, UP150.001.037.00001.00024 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 22, UP150.001.037.00001.00025 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 23, UP150.001.037.00001.00026 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 24, UP150.001.037.00001.00027 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 25, UP150.001.037.00001.00028 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 26, UP150.001.037.00001.00029 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 27, UP150.001.037.00001.00030 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 28, UP150.001.037.00001.00031 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 29, UP150.001.037.00001.00032 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 30, UP150.001.037.00001.00033 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 31, UP150.001.037.00001.00034 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 32, UP150.001.037.00001.00035 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 33, UP150.001.037.00001.00036 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 34, UP150.001.037.00001.00037 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 35, UP150.001.037.00001.00038 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 36, UP150.001.037.00001.00039 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 37, UP150.001.037.00001.00040 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 38, UP150.001.037.00001.00041 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 39, UP150.001.037.00001.00042 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 40, UP150.001.037.00001.00043 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 41, UP150.001.037.00001.00044 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 42, UP150.001.037.00001.00045 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 43, UP150.001.037.00001.00046 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 44, UP150.001.037.00001.00047 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 45, UP150.001.037.00001.00048 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 46, UP150.001.037.00001.00049 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 47, UP150.001.037.00001.00050 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 48, UP150.001.037.00001.00051 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 49, UP150.001.037.00001.00052 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 50, UP150.001.037.00001.00053 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 51, UP150.001.037.00001.00054 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 52, UP150.001.037.00001.00055 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 53, UP150.001.037.00001.00056 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 54, UP150.001.037.00001.00057 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 55, UP150.001.037.00001.00058 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 56, UP150.001.037.00001.00059 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 57, UP150.001.037.00001.00060 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 58, UP150.001.037.00001.00061 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 59, UP150.001.037.00001.00062 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 60, UP150.001.037.00001.00063 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 61, UP150.001.037.00001.00064 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 62, UP150.001.037.00001.00065 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 63, UP150.001.037.00001.00066 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 64, UP150.001.037.00001.00067 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 65, UP150.001.037.00001.00068 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 66, UP150.001.037.00001.00069 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 67, UP150.001.037.00001.00070 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 68, UP150.001.037.00001.00071 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 69, UP150.001.037.00001.00072 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 70, UP150.001.037.00001.00073 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 71, UP150.001.037.00001.00074 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 72, UP150.001.037.00001.00075 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 73, UP150.001.037.00001.00076 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 74, UP150.001.037.00001.00077 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 75, UP150.001.037.00001.00078 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 76, UP150.001.037.00001.00079 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 77, UP150.001.037.00001.00080 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 78, UP150.001.037.00001.00081 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 79, UP150.001.037.00001.00082 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 80, UP150.001.037.00001.00083 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 81, UP150.001.037.00001.00084 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 82, UP150.001.037.00001.00085 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 83, UP150.001.037.00001.00086 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 84, UP150.001.037.00001.00087 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 85, UP150.001.037.00001.00088 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 86, UP150.001.037.00001.00089 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 87, UP150.001.037.00001.00090 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 88, UP150.001.037.00001.00091 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 89, UP150.001.037.00001.00092 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 90, UP150.001.037.00001.00093 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 91, UP150.001.037.00001.00094 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 92, UP150.001.037.00001.00095 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 93, UP150.001.037.00001.00096 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 94, UP150.001.037.00001.00097 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 95, UP150.001.037.00001.00098 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, page 96, UP150.001.037.00001.00099 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, inside back cover (1), UP150.001.037.00001.00100 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, inside back cover (2), UP150.001.037.00001.00101 (Volume 37)
    - Tufts Medical 1978, back cover, UP150.001.037.00001.00102 (Volume 37)
  - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001 (Volume 38)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1979.
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, front cover, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00001 (Volume 38)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1979
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, inside front cover, left, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00002 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, inside front cover, right, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00003 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 1, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00004 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 2, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00005 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 3, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00006 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 4, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00007 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 5, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00008 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 6, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00009 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 7, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00010 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 8, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00011 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 9, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00012 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 10, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00013 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 11, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00014 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 12, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00015 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 13, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00016 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 14, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00017 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 15, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00018 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 16, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00019 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 17, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00020 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 18, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00021 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 19, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00022 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 20, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00023 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 21, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00024 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 22, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00025 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 23, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00026 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 24, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00027 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 25, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00028 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 26, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00029 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 27, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00030 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 28, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00031 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 29, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00032 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 30, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00033 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 31, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00034 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 32, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00035 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 33, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00036 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 34, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00037 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 35, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00038 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 36, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00039 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 37, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00040 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 38, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00041 (Volume 38)
    - Tufts Medical School M'79 Yearbook, page 39, 1979; UP150.001.038.00001.00042 (Volume 38)